the icici general insurance stock quoted
a 52-week of high
rupees 1440 and a 50
week of low rupees 805
valuation ratio according to bsc data
companies are virtually debt-free
company has been maintaining
a healthy dividend payout of 21.87
stock is trading at 9.49 times
to its book value market cap of company
store at rupees 57
284 on july
2020 shareholding pattern
as of 31st march 2020 foreign
institutional
investors fi held 23.39
taking the company while the promoter
held 55.86 percent taking the company
icici general insurance company
scheduled to announce
its march quite earning report on 17
july
2020 icsci general insurance
is one of the leading private sector
general insurance company in india
with a gross return premium gwp
of 1.47.89 billion
for the year ended march 31st
2019 and finally to avoid use losses in
the stock market
please ensure a strict stop loss and
thanks for your worth of confidence